Wow, love that blazer!
You'd look right at home on a TV show.
Yeah?
Yup.
It looks great on ya.
You're our pride and joy, Mitsumi-chan.
Pride and joy...
Anyway, I gotta run.
Can't be late for the entrance
ceremony, ya know?
Later!
Yeah, bye.
Call Ended
I'm Iwakura Mitsumi, fifteen years old.
And my life as a Tokyo
high schooler starts today!
I came here from a tiny, remote town
on the border of Ishikawa Prefecture.
Mitsumi-chan!
I'll be back for summer break!
Break a leg!
Take care!
I wish I coulda sent you off like that.
Haha, I know that feeling.
The nearest train line got shut down
more than a decade ago.
My middle school only had
eight students in my year.
Here, Mitsumi-chan.
Fumi-chan and I have been
together since kindergarten.
Cute.
I know you like pandas.
If you see Liang Liang, send me pics.
She's my best friend.
You got it.
Growing up with my best friend.
How cool is that?
Alarm
Snooze
Stop
Heh. Perfect.
Listen, Mitsu.
Change trains at the third stop, 'kay?
This is Nao-chan, my dad's sibling.
If anyone strange talks to you,
just ignore them.
She's taking care of me while I'm in Tokyo.
You worry too much, Nao-chan.
Can you blame me?
You only just found out that there's
more than one railway company!
I wish I could go with you,
but my work starts early today!
Relax.
My intuition tells me that today
will be nothing short of perfect.
Confi
dent
Plenty of time.
It won't just be today.
There will be zero screwups for the
entirety of my time in high school.
Why? Because I have
a clear road map for my life!
I will obviously go to Tokyo U,
attend law school,
and graduate as valedictorian.
I'll join the Ministry of Internal Affairs
and build a career there providing
key solutions to rural depopulation.
After I retire, I'll return to my
hometown and become mayor there,
using the knowledge from my career
to greatly improve our finances.
And when I die, I'll have my ashes
scattered in the Sea of Japan.
In the next three years, I'll develop
the brains I need to fulfill those ambitions!
However, my family doesn't
really get it, which is why...
Are you having fun at school?
Made any friends?
They'll probably worry about those things,
so I'll try to put them at ease, too.
Just wait and see, you guys.
Ikajima Town's prodigy, your pride and joy,
will return to you as a total big shot!
Third stop, third stop...
The entrance ceremony for Tsubame
West High School will now begin.
Please welcome the new first-years.
Hey, Sousuke?
Where are you?
Changing trains now.
Taking it easy, huh?
The entrance ceremony's already started.
Oh, really?
Maybe I should just go home, then.
At least try to get here, dude.
But...
I probably won't make...
She's stuck.
Wha?
A girl in our uniform.
She's stuck to the wall.
She crazy, you think?
Beats me. Why don't you ask her?
I gotta go, so I'm hanging up.
Are you a first-year?
Yes.
The others have already entered.
Sorry. I was fighting for my life in there.
Get going!
Yes, sir.
You still can't reach her?
No...
What do we do?
What's going on with Class 3?
Huh? Where am I?
Do I go that way? This way?
I got lost...
Got caught in rush hour...
And got sick from the crowd.
This wasn't the plan.
I wanna die.
Hey...
Are you okay?
Yikes!
Actually, never mind.
Eek!
H...
H-Huh?
How many years has it been
since I spoke to a stranger my age?
How...
How do I get to school from here?!
Oh, you're lost?
I'm running late, too.
Let's go together.
High school, college, and employment...
They're, uh... all about
the people you meet.
Er...
After passing our rigorous
entrance exams, uhm...
Oh, really? You're from Ishikawa?
Yes...
Which city?
I've never been to Ishikawa.
What if I don't make it in time?
Home
I know I'm gonna get
a call from home today.
They'll ask how the entrance ceremony went.
If I tell the truth, they'll worry about me.
Should I lie?
About all of it?
Hey, it's not the end of the world.
It's just the entrance ceremony.
Maybe that's all it is to you!
W-Wait, no!
We will soon be making
a brief stop at Miyamaeyama.
Oh, here's our stop.
The doors on the right side will open.
Touch here
It's about a ten-minute walk from here.
But you're in a rush, right?
Wanna run?
Dad. Mom.
Maharu. Kippei.
Granny. Satonosuke.
Omiso. Oshio.
Everything in Tokyo moves at lightning speed.
I got swallowed by its waves.
I panicked, made things worse,
and in the end...
It's straight down this road. Hang in there.
I lashed out at this kind, helpful guy.
I feel like I've seen my own
true colors in just half a day.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Y-You okay?
I'm... fine...
But for now, I'm gonna forget all that...
and run for my life!
Scene 01: Sparkling-Fresh
Oh!
Iwakura-san?!
...es...
Shima-kun?
Yes. Sorry we're late.
Sor...
There, there. I'm glad you made it.
Wait, are you okay, Iwakura-san?
Did I... make...
Yikes!
Yes, you're just in time.
Be sure to thank the person
we asked to sub in for you.
I will. I'm sorry.
Hmm?
Representing the incoming class,
Iwakura Mitsumi.
Yes!
You're top of the class?
Urk.
"Urk"?
Wait, did she forget her script?!
Speech
As the warmth of spring rolls in,
we 216 students stand here at the entrance
ceremony for Tsubame West High School.
On behalf of my class, I would like to
thank you all for this wonderful ceremony.
She memorized it?
Whoa.
Our hearts are filled with hopes and fears,
just like the sakura trees in the school
courtyard, with flowers yet to blossom.
The experience of overcoming
the tough entrance exams
will give us confidence and strength
to overcome the days ahead.
Haha...
None of us could have made it this far alone.
We must remember the support we
received from our families and friends,
try to live up to their expectations,
and in our time at Tsubame West,
think for ourselves...
I'm blessed to join a school that values
independence, individuality, and autonomy.
And, last but not least,
to the teachers and the older students:
We hope that you will watch over
and guide us new students.
Thank you.
She didn't blink once!
Extreme anxiety
That mad
dash earlier
Lack of sleep
Iwakura-san? Where are you go—
Huh?
Favorite Blouse:
Brand-New Suit:
10,000 yen
45,000 yen
The Script for Today
The script for today:
One.
Two.
That was a great speech!
Three.
Let's be friends!
Oh, the puker?
This is concerning.
The puker, huh?
Day one, and I'm the puker.
But wait, I can salvage that if I try.
Oh, I listen to them, too!
Aren't they great?
Hey, let's trade contact details.
Really? I'd love to.
Did you get it?
Hah, what is this sticker? It's cute!
W-Wow. I should learn from them.
Hey!
I-It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, same here.
I feel like she just brushed me off.
By the way, did you watch their
Pinsta Live a couple of days ago?
Iwakura-san.
I only realized towards the end.
Guess we're in the same class.
Shima-kun?
That's right. You feeling any better?
Much better now that I hurled.
Oh, good to hear.
I knew it.
I loved your speech. You bossed it up out there.
This guy's a saint!
You weren't even reading notes, were you?
I could never write a speech
like that to save my life.
Oh, I'm suddenly even
finding his face lovely.
I really thought you were amazing.
Is it because he helped me so much today?
Or is Tokyo just filled with
dreamy people like him?
*It isn't
Oh, boy, major stud alert!
He doesn't seem too conceited.
Wonder if he has a girlfriend.
He wasn't in the procession, was he?
I'm so glad I'm in this class.
Iwakura-san, let's be friends.
Oh, give me your ID and stuff.
I'll text you.
Friends
Gimme your ID, too.
Oh, I'm Egashira Mika.
I sit right behind you, so I wanna
get to know you better.
I guess my timing was just off earlier.
Sure.
You're Mitsumi-chan? That's a cute name.
Take your seats, everyone.
Sorry I'm late. I had a lot going on.
Forgive me.
I'm Hanazono Sakura,
and I'm in charge of Class 3.
This is my first time as homeroom teacher,
so I'm sure I'll need your help,
but I promise you I'll do my best!
I'm looking forward to working with you all!
Today, I'll give you a simple
intro to your textbooks,
and you'll fill out these profile sheets.
After that, you're free to go.
Tomorrow, you'll introduce
yourselves to the class.
Now, then.
I wonder what my classmates are like.
I'd like to build some solid
relationships with them.
And that's about it, yeah.
No major incidents.
My day was a total success.
Good for ya!
Meanwhile, I was so nervous, I couldn't
respond to people who talked to me.
It's just the first day.
You'll be fine, Fumi.
Ya think? Did ya manage to talk to anyone?
Get this. I made two friends.
Oh, wow! What're they like?
A cute, stylish girl,
and a really nice guy.
Whoa! A guy?!
No way! How?
He helped me this morning when I was los—
er, was close to going the wrong way.
And we wound up in the same class.
Wow... Is he hot?
Ho—
I guess. I've never met
anyone like him before.
Very dapper.
Whoa, lucky you!
But, man, I'd be so lonely
if you got a boyfriend.
Come on, quit jumping the gun!
I better give it my all from tomorrow, too.
Yeah, I'm rooting for you.
I'm home.
Oh, Nao-chan's back.
I'll letcha go, then.
Oh, and take care of my siblings, please?
I'm sure they're gonna miss having me around.
Sure!
Welcome home, Nao-chan.
Sorry I'm late!
How was the entrance ceremony?
It went well.
Really? Thank goodness!
Were you on the phone?
Yeah, was talking to Fumi.
She's feeling helpless
on her own, as expected.
She always has her head in the clouds,
so I worry about her.
Right.
Come, let's eat while we chat.
I bought dinner from
a fancy deli to celebrate.
Thanks!
A deli? Wow, these sides are stylin'.
This place makes the yummiest stuff.
Do kids even say "stylin'" these days?
Yum!
Good evening!
Satonosuke!
Hey there, Fumi-chan.
Brought you some radishes from Mom.
These are so fresh! Thank you!
Oh, do your folks need any asparagus?
I'll fetch some in two
shakes of a lamb's tail.
Fumi-chan, Fumi-chan!
Didya phone Sis?
I just did, yeah.
She say anything?
Like what?
Like, she tells us her day went perfect,
but we were thinking she probably
got lost at the station or something.
I was worried about the same thing.
She's got a screw loose when it comes
to anything 'sides her studies.
Here.
Wow, that's a lot. Thank you.
It'll be fine.
She was happily saying
she made some new pals.
And I'll phone her regularly
to check up on her.
Thank you, dear.
I'll be off, then. Have a good night.
I'd feel a lot better
if Fumi-chan were there with her.
Right?
How was your entrance ceremony?
My class is looking pretty good.
Lucky you.
Mine had this awkward mood from day one.
Hey, don't take my shrimp! I only had four...
Don't be a cheapskate.
Your uniform is real cute.
How about you, Sousuke?
Hmm?
Yeah. How's your little elite school?
I overslept, for one thing.
That was quick!
You didn't make it?
No, I did. I ran from the station.
Who, you?
Yeah.
I thought there wouldn't be a chance in hell,
but the principal's speech
apparently went forever,
so we ended up making it.
That was kinda fun, honestly.
Was it with a girl?
Oh, I should get going.
Lemme out.
Huh?!
Wait, you're leaving already?
Are you serious?
Was it really a girl? That was fast!
Hey, don't run away.
Nah, just thought I'd go home early.
Wouldn't want to be late tomorrow, you know?
Later.
The heck was that?
Don't ask me.
Something must've made him
really happy today.
Yeah.
I might as well enjoy my high school life.
The night lights are so bright here.
Today's mistakes don't count.
It was only my first day, after all.
Also, I did study for the post-entrance exam
and did a bunch of my spring homework.
All good.
I'll be fine from tomorrow.
I know it.
Self-introductions, huh?
Won't be a problem, obviously.
But maybe I should figure out
what I'm gonna say.
First impressions are key.
I'll prepare multiple options
based on the class's mood.
Oh, good morning, Mitsu...
First impressions are...
Yikes!